autobacklinkbuilder.com 2019-04-01

# Terms and Privacy Policy | KOKOSHUNGSAN-Marketing Solution & Multiple Income Sources

## Kokoshungsan Ltd. Terms of Service and Privacy Policy

### The website

This website and its owners take a proactive approach to user privacy and ensure the necessary steps are taken to protect the privacy of its users throughout their visiting experience. This website complies with all UK national laws and requirements for user privacy.

### 1\. Terms

By accessing the website at [https://kokoshungsan.net](https://kokoshungsan.net/), you are agreeing to be bound by these terms of service, all applicable laws and regulations, and agree that you are responsible for compliance with any applicable local laws. If you do not agree with any of these terms, you are prohibited from using or accessing this site. The materials contained in this website are protected by applicable copyright and trademark law.

### 2\. Use License

  1. Permission is granted to temporarily download one copy of the materials (information or software) on Kokoshungsan Ltd.’s website for personal, non-commercial transitory viewing only. This is the grant of a license, not a transfer of title, and under this license you may not:
    1. modify or copy the materials;
    2. use the materials for any commercial purpose, or for any public display (commercial or non-commercial);
    3. attempt to decompile or reverse engineer any software contained on Kokoshungsan Ltd.’s website;
    4. remove any copyright or other proprietary notations from the materials; or
    5. transfer the materials to another person or “mirror” the materials on any other server.
  2. This license shall automatically terminate if you violate any of these restrictions and may be terminated by Kokoshungsan Ltd. at any time. Upon terminating your viewing of these materials or upon the termination of this license, you must destroy any downloaded materials in your possession whether in electronic or printed format.

### 3\. Disclaimer

  1. The materials on Kokoshungsan Ltd.’s website are provided on an ‘as is’ basis. Kokoshungsan Ltd. makes no warranties, expressed or implied, and hereby disclaims and negates all other warranties including, without limitation, implied warranties or conditions of merchantability, fitness for a particular purpose, or non-infringement of intellectual property or other violation of rights.
  2. Further, Kokoshungsan Ltd. does not warrant or make any representations concerning the accuracy, likely results, or reliability of the use of the materials on its website or otherwise relating to such materials or on any sites linked to this site.

### 4\. Limitations

In no event shall Kokoshungsan Ltd. or its suppliers be liable for any damages (including, without limitation, damages for loss of data or profit, or due to business interruption) arising out of the use or inability to use the materials on Kokoshungsan Ltd.’s website, even if Kokoshungsan Ltd. or a Kokoshungsan Ltd. authorized representative has been notified orally or in writing of the possibility of such damage. Because some jurisdictions do not allow limitations on implied warranties, or limitations of liability for consequential or incidental damages, these limitations may not apply to you.

### 5\. Accuracy of materials

The materials appearing on Kokoshungsan Ltd.’s website could include technical, typographical, or photographic errors. Kokoshungsan Ltd. does not warrant that any of the materials on its website are accurate, complete or current. Kokoshungsan Ltd. may make changes to the materials contained on its website at any time without notice. However Kokoshungsan Ltd. does not make any commitment to update the materials.

### 6\. Links

Kokoshungsan Ltd. has not reviewed all of the sites linked to its website and is not responsible for the contents of any such linked site. The inclusion of any link does not imply endorsement by Kokoshungsan Ltd. of the site. Use of any such linked website is at the user’s own risk.

### 7\. Modifications

Kokoshungsan Ltd. may revise these terms of service for its website at any time without notice. By using this website you are agreeing to be bound by the then current version of these terms of service.

### 8\. Governing Law

These terms and conditions are governed by and construed in accordance with the laws of UK and you irrevocably submit to the exclusive jurisdiction of the courts in that State or location.

### 9.Earnings Disclaimer

While we make every effort to ensure that we accurately represent all the products and services reviewed on this website and their potential for income, it should be noted that earnings and income statements made by kokoshungsan.net and its advertisers/sponsors are estimates only of what we think you can possibly earn. There is no guarantee that you will make these levels of income and you accept the risk that the earnings and income statements differ by individual.

As with any business, your results may vary and will be based on your individual capacity, business experience, expertise, and level of desire. There are no guarantees concerning the level of success you may experience. The testimonials and examples used are exceptional results, which do not apply to the average purchaser and are not intended to represent or guarantee that anyone will achieve the same or similar results. Each individual’s success depends on his or her background, dedication, desire and motivation.

There is no assurance that examples of past earnings can be duplicated in the future. We cannot guarantee your future results and/or success. There are some unknown risks in business and on the internet that we cannot foresee which could reduce results you experience. We are not responsible for your actions.

The use of our information, products and services should be based on your own due diligence and you agree that kokoshungsan.net and the advertisers/sponsors of this website are not liable for any success or failure of your business that is directly or indirectly related to the purchase and use of our information, products, and services reviewed or advertised on this website.

## Privacy Policy

Your privacy is important to us.

It is Kokoshungsan Ltd.’s policy to respect your privacy regarding any information we may collect while operating our website. Accordingly, we have developed this privacy policy in order for you to understand how we collect, use, communicate, disclose and otherwise make use of personal information. We have outlined our privacy policy below.

  * We will collect personal information by lawful and fair means and, where appropriate, with the knowledge or consent of the individual concerned.
  * Before or at the time of collecting personal information, we will identify the purposes for which information is being collected.
  * We will collect and use personal information solely for fulfilling those purposes specified by us and for other ancillary purposes, unless we obtain the consent of the individual concerned or as required by law.
  * Personal data should be relevant to the purposes for which it is to be used, and, to the extent necessary for those purposes, should be accurate, complete, and up-to-date.
  * We will protect personal information by using reasonable security safeguards against loss or theft, as well as unauthorized access, disclosure, copying, use or modification.
  * We will make readily available to customers information about our policies and practices relating to the management of personal information.
  * We will only retain personal information for as long as necessary for the fulfilment of those purposes.

We are committed to conducting our business in accordance with these principles in order to ensure that the confidentiality of personal information is protected and maintained. Kokoshungsan Ltd. may change this privacy policy from time to time at Kokoshungsan Ltd.’s sole discretion.

 **KOKOSHUNGSAN LTD. PRIVACY POLICY**

 **PLEASE READ THE FOLLOWING PRIVACY POLICY CAREFULLY BEFORE DOWNLOADING, USING, ACCESSING, OR PURCHASING ANY PRODUCT OR SERVICE THROUGH, ANY PART OF THE KOKOSHUNGSAN** **  WEBSITE OR SERVICES, THE KOKOSHUNGSAN AFFILIATE PROGRAM, OR THE KOKOSHUNGSAN MOBILE APPLICATION (IF AVAILABLE)**

 **I. OVERVIEW**

Kokoshungsan Ltd. (“Kokoshungsan,” “us,” or “we”) respects the privacy of users of Kokoshungsan Ltd. ‘s website www.kokoshungsan.net and its related services, including the Kokoshungsan platform and Affiliate Program (the “Website”) and the Kokoshungsan Mobile Application (if available) and its services (the “Application”) (collectively the Website and the Application are referred to as the “Services”). The following privacy policy (the “Policy”) tells you about the information that Kokoshungsan collects through the Services and how Kokoshungsan may use or disclose that collected information.

By accessing the Services, continuing to access the Services, purchasing any products or services through the Services, downloading and/or using the Application, or submitting any information through the Services, you are consenting to the information collection and use practices described in this Policy, as modified from time to time by us, as described below. Your use of the Services is also governed by the Terms of Service, and may be governed by the Affiliate Agreement or Seller Agreement, all of which are expressly incorporated into this Policy.

Sellers, affiliates, and users may collect information from or about other sellers, affiliates, or users outside of the Services. A seller’s, affiliate’s, or user’s collection, use, and disclosure of information will be governed by their own privacy policy.

 **II. UPDATES**

Kokoshungsan reserves the right to make changes to this Policy at any time and will post any revised Policy on this page. You will know we have changed the Policy when you see a new updated date at the top of this Policy. Kokoshungsan will not notify the Services’ users of any such changes by email or another personal contact. We encourage you to check the date of this Policy whenever you visit the Services so that you will know when you need to review the Policy for modifications.

 **III. INFORMATION COLLECTION**

 **Age Restriction.** Kokoshungsan does not intend to use the Services to collect any information from children under age 18. By submitting any information through the Services, you represent and warrant that you are older than age 18.

 **Collection of Submitted Information.** Kokoshungsan may collect and store any information you submit or upload through the Services, whether through your submission of information through a form, purchase of a product, or otherwise. This information may include but is not limited to, your name, address, email address, telephone number, payment information, or any other information submitted by you or any user through the Services.

 **Collection from Third-Parties.** Kokoshungsan may collect information about you from third-parties, including from an account through which you log into, or otherwise interact with, Kokoshungsan (e.g., Facebook or Google). If applicable, Kokoshungsan may have access to certain information from your linked Google or Facebook account, including your public profile information, your email address, or other information possessed by those third-parties. Kokoshungsan may aggregate any information about you collected from any source.

 **Passive Information Collection.** Kokoshungsan may also collect passive information about your device, visit, or use of the Services, including, but not limited to, the date and time of your visit, the length of your visit, the specific webpages you visited, your IP address, the type of web browser and operating system used, the address of any website that directed you to the Services, and information about your mobile device used to access the Services (including phone number, operating system details, and any applicable unique identifiers for you or your device, including your devices’ Unique Device Identifier (UDID), any Apple or iOS identifiers (e.g., IDFA or an Advertising Identifier), any Google or Android identifiers (e.g., Android or Google Advertising ID), any Windows identifiers (e.g., Windows Advertising ID), or any other similar identifiers which identify you or your device). Kokoshungsan may collect and aggregate usage information related to your use of the Services.

 **Cookies and Related Technologies.**  We, or other third-parties assisting us, may use cookies, web beacons, local shared objects (sometimes called “flash cookies”), or other similar technology in connection with your use of the Services (collectively, “Cookies”). Cookies are small data files that may have unique identifiers, and reside, among other places, on your computer or mobile device, in emails we send to you, and on our web pages. Cookies may transmit information about you and your use of the Services, such as your browser type, search preferences, data relating to advertisements that have been displayed to you or that you have clicked on, and the date and time of your use. Cookies may track activities over time and across websites. You can disable some (but not all) Cookies in your device or browser settings, but doing so may affect your ability to use the services provided through the Services.

 **Third-Party Vendors and Advertisers.** Kokoshungsan may use third-party vendors or advertisers to collect and analyze information about your use of the Services. These third-parties may use cookies or other similar mechanisms to provide us with information and analysis about your use of the Services. This information collection and analysis allows us to better understand how the Services are being used so that we can strive to provide the most relevant content to our users. These third-parties may collect information about your online activities over time and across different websites. This information may be used to serve interest-based advertisements on our website or other websites across the internet. We may combine information gathered from one or more of these services.

 **Analytics Services.** Kokoshungsan may, from time to time, use one or more analytics service providers, including, for example, Google or Facebook. Kokoshungsan may use the following Google analytics features: AdWords, Remarketing, Google Display Network Impression Reporting, DoubleClick, and Google Analytics Demographics and Interest Reporting. We may combine information gathered from one or more of these services.

For information on how Google collects and uses the information collected through Kokoshungsan’ use of the Google analytics and advertising services, if applicable, see the Google, Inc. Privacy Policy here (https://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/).

For more information about the Google analytics features used by Kokoshungsan if applicable, click here (https://support.google.com/analytics/answer/2404395?hl=en&ref_topic=1631776&rd=1).

For information on how to see and change your Google Ad Settings, click here (https://support.google.com/ads/answer/2662856?hl=en).

For information on the use of the Google Analytics Opt-Out Browser Add-On, click here (https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/). However, Kokoshungsan does not necessarily endorse this add-on and does not guarantee that using the add-on will be effective.

For more information on how Facebook Analytics may collect and use the information collected through Kokoshungsan’s use of the Facebook’s analytics and advertising services, if applicable, see the Facebook data use policy and related policies here. (https://www.facebook.com/full_data_use_policy).

The Services may, from time to time, also include social media functions allowing you to like or share content on social media platforms like Facebook or Twitter. These features may collect your information through the use of cookies or other technologies. These features may be hosted by a third-party and governed by the third-party’s privacy policy.

Kokoshungsan does not guarantee that it will take action in response to do-not-track signals or similar mechanisms. Additionally, some third-party service providers may still collect tracking information even if you have enabled your browser’s do-not-track functionality or utilized a similar do-not-track mechanism.

 **IV. INFORMATION USE PRACTICES**

Kokoshungsan may use the collected information or data described above, individually or in the aggregate, for any lawful purpose, including, but not limited to, such purposes as connecting sellers, affiliates, and customers, analyzing and tracking user activity on the Services for individual users or for groups of users, tracking and analyzing usage trends, personalizing the Services to better reflect your preferences, serving more relevant advertisements, or enhancing your and other users’ use of the Services. All collected information may be linked to specific website users and may result in the tracking of the usage information for individual users.

 **Kokoshungsan may also use your submitted information to contact you, via regular mail, email, text message, telephone, or otherwise, regarding your account, the Services, your purchased services or products, or other relevant or promotional information or offers as determined by Kokoshungsan or its partners. By submitting your contact information to Kokoshungsan or Kokoshungsan’ partners, you consent to receive such communications.**

 **V. DISCLOSURE OF INFORMATION**

Except for the limitations expressly discussed herein, if any, Kokoshungsan may disclose, sell, or transfer any collected information to third-parties for any lawful purpose in our sole discretion.

 **Disclosure of Customer, Affiliate, or Seller Information.** Kokoshungsan may disclose any collected information about a customer to all sellers whose products or services the customer purchases and to any affiliates through whom the customer is linked to the seller. Kokoshungsan may disclose any collected information about an affiliate to all sellers whose products or services the affiliate advertises and to any customers that were linked to a seller through the affiliate. Kokoshungsan may disclose any collected information about a seller to any affiliates and to any customers who purchase the seller’s products or services. The disclosed information about a customer, affiliate, or seller include but are not limited to, the person’s name, username, contact information, and information related to any transactions between those persons.

 **Third-Party Services.**  If you log in to Kokoshungsan through a third-party service like Facebook or Google, then those third-parties may have access to certain information about your use of Kokoshungsan. For more information on the type of information those third-parties may collect about you, please review the privacy policies for those third-parties.

 **Vendors.** Kokoshungsan may use third-party companies, agents, or contractors to perform services on our behalf. For example, Kokoshungsan may partner with other companies to personalize our web pages, analyze our website or usage information, process payments or credit card transactions, fulfill or ship orders, collect debts, analyze or enhance the data collected by the Services (including user’s interaction with the Services), or otherwise assist Kokoshungsan in better serving the Services’ users. During the course of providing Kokoshungsan with these services, these third-parties may have access to your personal and non-personal information in order to provide the services we requested from those third-parties.

 **Affiliates and Marketing.** Kokoshungsan may disclose your collected information, including information about any purchases you make through the Services, to Kokoshungsan’ affiliated entities. Kokoshungsan may also disclose your information to third-parties for marketing purposes. These affiliates and third-parties may contact you via any method of contact you provide to Kokoshungsan.

 **Legal Compliance.** Kokoshungsan also reserves the right to disclose personal information when we reasonably believe disclosure is required by law if we reasonably believe disclosure is necessary to establish or exercise legal rights, or in situations involving potential threats to physical safety.

 **Merger or Acquisition.**  In the event that Kokoshungsanis acquired by or merged with a third-party, we reserve the right to sell or otherwise transfer any and all information we have collected from you as part of that transaction and such third-party will assume the rights and obligations with respect to that information as described in this Policy.

 **VI. THIRD-PARTY LINKS**

The Services may contain links to websites not owned or controlled by Kokoshungsan. Kokoshungsan does not necessarily review or endorse the content of these linked websites. You should review the terms of service and privacy policies of all websites you visit.

 **VII. SECURITY**

We use commercially reasonable efforts to protect the information we collect on the Services. Unfortunately, however, no security system can be guaranteed to be 100% effective. Accordingly, we cannot and do not guarantee the security of your personal information and cannot assume liability for improper access to it. Do not submit confidential information through the Services.

You are responsible for restricting access to your computer or mobile device through which you access the Services. Users of public or shared computers or unprotected mobile devices should log out at the completion of each visit to our Services. By using the Services, or providing personal information to us through any means, you agree that we can communicate with you electronically regarding security, privacy, and administrative issues relating to your use of these Services.

 **VIII. DATA RETENTION**

Kokoshungsan may retain the personal and non-personal information or other collected data, individually or in the aggregate, as described above after you delete your account or have ceased using the Services. However, Kokoshungsan does not guarantee that any information will continue to be available after such deletion or cessation.

### Use of cookies

###  **What are cookies?**

Cookies are small files saved to the user’s computer’s hard drive that track, save and store information about the user’s interactions and usage of the website. This allows the website, through its server to provide the users with a tailored experience within this website.

###  **What do we use cookies for?**

We may use cookies to remember personal settings you have chosen at our website. In no other context do we use cookies to collect information that identifies you personally. Most of the cookies we set are automatically deleted from your computer when you leave our website or shortly afterward.

We use anonymous session cookies (short-term cookies that disappear when you close your browser) to help you navigate the website and make the most of the features. If you log into the website, application or a course as a registered user, your session cookie will also contain your user ID so that we can check which services you are allowed to access.

This website uses tracking software to monitor its visitors to better understand how they use it. This software is provided by Google Analytics which uses cookies to track visitor usage. The software will save a cookie to your computer’s hard drive in order to track and monitor your engagement and usage of the website, but will not store, save or collect personal information.

Should users wish to deny the use and saving of cookies from this website onto their computer’s hard drive, they should take necessary steps within their web browser’s security settings to block all cookies from this website and its external serving vendors.

### Personal information

Whilst using our website, software applications or services, you may be required to provide personal information (name, address, email, account details, etc.). We will use this information to administer our website, applications, client databases and marketing material. We will ensure that all personal information supplied is held securely in accordance with the General Data Protection Regulation (EU) 2016/679, as adopted into law of the United Kingdom in the Data Protection Act 2018. Further, by providing telephone, fax, and email details, you consent to kokoshungsan Ltd contacting you using that method. You have the right at any time to request a copy of the personal information we hold on you. Should you wish to receive a copy of this, or would like to be removed from our database, please contact us at support@kokoshungsan.net.

### Information collection and use

###  **How do we collect information?**

kokoshungsan Ltd collects information in two possible ways:

  1.  _When you directly give it to us (“Directly Provided Data”)_

When you sign up for our site, purchase our products or communicate with us, you may choose to voluntarily give us certain information – for example, by filling in text boxes or completing registration forms. All this information requires a direct action by you at that time in order for us to receive it.

  1.  _When you give us permission to obtain from other accounts (“User Authorised Data”)_

Depending on your settings or the privacy policies for other online services, you may give us permission to obtain information from your account with those other services. For example, this can be via social media or by choosing to send us your location data when accessing our website from your smartphone.

 **How long do we keep your data for?**

kokoshungsan Ltd will not retain your personal information longer than necessary. We will hold onto the information you provide either while your account is in existence, or as needed to be able to provide the Services to you, or (in the case of any contact you may have with our Customer Care team) for as long as is necessary to provide support-related reporting and trend analysis only.

If legally required or if it is reasonably necessary to meet regulatory requirements, resolve disputes, prevent fraud and abuse, or enforce our Terms and Conditions, we may also retain some of your information for a limited period of time as required, even after you have closed your account or it is no longer needed to provide the Services to you.

### Registration forms

kokoshungsan Ltd will not sell or rent your personally identifiable information, gathered as a result of filling out the site registration form, to anyone.

###  **Choosing how we use your data**

We understand that you trust us with your personal information and we are committed to ensuring you can manage the privacy and security of your personal information yourself.

With respect to the information relating to you that ends up in our possession, and recognizing that it is your choice to provide us with your personally identifiable information, we commit to giving you the ability to do all of the following:

  * You can verify the details you have submitted to [company name] by contacting our customer services team support@kokoshungsan.net. Our security procedures mean that we may request proof of identity before we reveal information, including your e-mail address and possibly your address
  * You can also contact us by the same method to change, correct, or delete your personal information controlled by kokoshungsan Ltd regarding your profile at any time. Please note though that, if you have shared any information with others through social media channels, that information may remain visible, even if your account is deleted.
  * You are also free to close your account through our account settings. If you do so, your account will be deactivated. However, we may retain archived copies of your information as required by law or for legitimate business purposes (including to help address fraud and spam).
  * You can always feel free to update us on your details at any point by email at support@kokoshungsan.net.
  * You can unsubscribe from receiving marketing emails from us by clicking the “unsubscribe” link at the bottom of any email. Once you do this, you will no longer receive any emails from us.
  * You can request a readable copy of the personal data we hold on you at any time. To do this, please contact us support@kokoshungsan.net.

Please note, we are constantly reviewing how we process and protect data. Therefore, changes to our policy may occur at any time. We will endeavour to publicise any changes.

 **IX. VIEWING AND UPDATING INFORMATION**

You are responsible for updating and maintaining the accuracy of your personal information that you provide to or through the Services. If you believe you have submitted inaccurate information to the Services and would like KokoshungsanJVZoo to change such information, please contact Kokoshungsan at support@kokoshungsan.net
